Jesus said that if I thirst
I should come to Him
No one else can satisfy
Jesus said if I am weak
I should come to Him
No one else can be my strength
For the Lord is good and faithful
He will keep us day and night
We can always run to Jesus
Jesus strong and kind
Jesus said that if I fear
I should come to Him
No one else can be my shield
For the Lord is good and faithful
He will keep us day and night
We can always run to Jesus
Jesus strong and kind
Jesus said if I am lost
He will come to me
And He showed me on that cross
For the Lord is good and faithful
He will keep us day and night
We can always run to Jesus
Jesus strong and kind
For the Lord is good and faithful
He will keep us day and night
We can always run to Jesus
Jesus strong and kind